export const chapter = "Chapter - 4: Noun: Numbers and Gender";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "What is the Singular form of the word 'fairies'?",
          optionA: "fairys",
          optionB: "fairie",
          optionC: "fairy",
          correctAnswer: "C) fairy",
        },
        {
          question: "How are most Singular Nouns changed into Plural?",
          optionA: "Adding -ies",
          optionB: "Adding -s",
          optionC: "Adding -es",
          correctAnswer: "B) Adding -s",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the Plural form of the word ending in 'ch'?",
          optionA: "knife",
          optionB: "toffee",
          optionC: "knives",
          correctAnswer: "C) knives",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How are Singular Nouns ending in 'y' preceded by a Consonant changed into Plural?",
          optionA: "Adding -ies",
          optionB: "Dropping y and adding -ies",
          optionC: "Adding -s",
          correctAnswer: "B) Dropping y and adding -ies",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is true for Singular Nouns ending in 'o' preceded by a Consonant?",
          optionA: "Add -es to them",
          optionB: "Add -s to them",
          optionC: "Both A and B",
          correctAnswer: "A) Add -es to them",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What happens to Singular Nouns ending in 'f' or 'fe' to change into Plural?",
          optionA: "Add -s",
          optionB: "Replace for fe by -ves",
          optionC: "Both A and B",
          correctAnswer: "C) Both A and B",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an exception when changing Singular Nouns ending in 'o' into Plural?",
          optionA: "Add -es",
          optionB: "Add -s",
          optionC: "Can take either -s or -es",
          correctAnswer: "B) Add -s",
        },
        {
          question: "How are Compound Nouns changed into Plural?",
          optionA: "Adding -s",
          optionB: "Changing the principal word",
          optionC: "Adding -es",
          correctAnswer: "B) Changing the principal word",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What type of Gender denotes that the Noun is without life?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Feminine Gender",
          optionC: "Neuter Gender",
          correctAnswer: "C) Neuter Gender",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How can we change a Noun in Masculine Gender into Feminine Gender?",
          optionA: "Add -ess at the end",
          optionB: "Remove the last vowel and add -ess",
          optionC: "Both A and B",
          correctAnswer: "C) Both A and B",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Singular Nouns ending in y preceded by a consonant are changed into Plural by dropping y and replacing it with _______.",
          optionA: "-ies",
          optionB: "-s",
          optionC: "-es",
          correctAnswer: "A) -ies",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Singular Nouns ending in o preceded by a consonant are changed into Plural by adding _______ to them.",
          optionA: "-es",
          optionB: "-s",
          optionC: "-ies",
          correctAnswer: "A) -es",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Singular Nouns ending in o can take either _______ or _______.",
          optionA: "-s",
          optionB: "-es",
          optionC: "-ies",
          correctAnswer: "A) -s; -es",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Compound Nouns are changed into Plural by changing the _______ word.",
          optionA: "principal",
          optionB: "secondary",
          optionC: "modifying",
          correctAnswer: "A) principal",
        },
        {
          question: "Neuter Gender denotes a Noun that is without _______.",
          optionA: "life",
          optionB: "gender",
          optionC: "plural",
          correctAnswer: "A) life",
        },
        {
          question:
            "We can change a Masculine Noun into Feminine by removing the last _______ and adding -ess.",
          optionA: "consonant",
          optionB: "vowel",
          optionC: "syllable",
          correctAnswer: "B) vowel",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Common Gender denotes a Noun that can be either _______ or _______.",
          optionA: "singular; plural",
          optionB: "male; female",
          optionC: "animate; inanimate",
          correctAnswer: "B) male; female",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Nouns ending in f or fe take only _______ to change into Plural.",
          optionA: "-s",
          optionB: "-es",
          optionC: "-ies",
          correctAnswer: "A) -s",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Changing Singular Nouns into Plural by adding -s is a general rule, but there are _______.",
          optionA: "exceptions",
          optionB: "variations",
          optionC: "alternatives",
          correctAnswer: "A) exceptions",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Personal names and titles are changed from Singular into Plural, as a _______.",
          optionA: "convention",
          optionB: "formality",
          optionC: "custom",
          correctAnswer: "C) custom",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Singular Nouns ending in y preceded by a consonant are changed into Plural by dropping y and replacing it with -ies.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Ijardari System was initially continued by the Company in Bengal, where revenue officials collected land revenue, deducted 10 percent as commission, and deposited the rest in the Company's treasury.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Mahalwari System, introduced in western Uttar Pradesh, parts of Madhya Pradesh, and Punjab, vested land ownership in a 'revenue estate' called Mahal.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Permanent Settlement system was introduced in Bengal and Bihar in 1793.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Under the Permanent Settlement, small rulers were made farmers, and the revenue they had to pay to the Company was fixed on a permanent basis.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Some Singular Nouns ending in o can take either -s or -es.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Neuter Gender denotes a Noun that is without life.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "We can change a Masculine Noun into Feminine by removing the last consonant and adding -ess.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Compound Nouns are changed into Plural by changing the secondary word.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Company's officers were often more interested in their own political influence than the welfare of the people.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
